<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Wiki en.wikipedia.org</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org</link><description>Hi</description><atom:link href="https://en.wikipedia.org" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:30:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Kenardo Forbes</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kenardo_Forbes</link><description>Kenardo Forbes (born 15 May 1988) is a Jamaican retired footballer who played as a midfielder.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kenardo_Forbes</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Borys Shchokin</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Borys_Shchokin</link><description>Borys Mikhailovych Shchokin (Russian: Борис Михайлович Щёкин; May 2, 1945 – June 16, 2017) was a Ukrainian scientist, researcher and teacher who worked in the field of Electromechanical systems and Engineering.[1][2][3][4]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Borys_Shchokin</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lars Høgh</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lars_H%C3%B8gh</link><description>Poul Lars Høgh-Pedersen (Danish pronunciation: [ˈhøːˀj]; 14 January 1959 – 8 December 2021) was a Danish footballer, who played his entire career as a goalkeeper for Odense BK. He won three Danish football championships and three Danish Cup trophies with OB, and won the Danish Best Goalkeeper of the Year award five times. He played eight matches for the Denmark national team, and was selected for the 1986 World Cup and 1996 European Championship squads. He was a part of the Danish team which won the 1995 King Fahd Cup.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lars_H%C3%B8gh</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Norman Bassette</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Norman_Bassette</link><description>Norman Jaquy Bassette (born 9 November 2004) is a Belgian professional footballer who plays as a forward for German 2. Bundesliga club 1. FC Kaiserslautern on loan from EFL Championship club Coventry City and the Belgium national team.[1]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Norman_Bassette</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Greeks Had a Word for Them</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Greeks_Had_a_Word_for_Them</link><description>The Greeks Had a Word for Them (also known as Three Broadway Girls) is a 1932 American pre-Code comedy film directed by Lowell Sherman, produced by Samuel Goldwyn, and released by United Artists. It stars Ina Claire, Joan Blondell, and Madge Evans and is based on the play The Greeks Had a Word for It by Zoe Akins. The studio originally wanted actress Jean Harlow for the lead after her success in Public Enemy (1931[2]), but she was under contract to Howard Hughes, and he refused to loan her out. The film served as inspiration for films such as Three Blind Mice (1938), Moon Over Miami (1941), and How to Marry a Millionaire (1953).[3][4] Ladies in Love (1936) also has a similar pattern and was produced like "Three Blind Mice" by Darryl F. Zanuck.[clarification needed]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Greeks_Had_a_Word_for_Them</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>