<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Wiki en.wikipedia.org</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org</link><description>Hi</description><atom:link href="https://en.wikipedia.org" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:33:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Watampone</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Watampone</link><description>Watampone is a town in South Sulawesi province of Indonesia and the capital of Bone Regency. Known colloquially as Bone, it has a land area of 126.35 km2 and had a population of 149,336 at the 2020 Census;[1][2] the official estimate as of mid-2023 was 151,554.[3] It is divided administratively into three districts (kecamatan) within the Bone Regency - West Tanate Riattang, Tanate Riattang, and East Tanate Riattang. It is also the birthplace of the 10th and 12th Vice President of the Republic of Indonesia Jusuf Kalla.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Watampone</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bethel Baptist Church (Houston, Texas)</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bethel_Baptist_Church_(Houston,_Texas)</link><description>Bethel Baptist Church is a historic Baptist church building at 801 Andrews in the Fourth Ward, Houston, Texas.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bethel_Baptist_Church_(Houston,_Texas)</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vulcan Bowl</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vulcan_Bowl</link><description>The Vulcan Bowl was a college football bowl game played at Rickwood Field in Birmingham, Alabama. The game was played on New Year's Day between 1941 and 1949 and again in 1952, between historically black colleges and universities (HBCUs). The game was one of the longer-lasting bowls for HBCUs established in the 1940s.[1] The first game in the series was called the Steel Bowl, and the bowl game served as an early era black college football national championship game by matching the Southern Intercollegiate Athletic Conference champion against the best team from the other HBCU conferences.[2] The final contest was also called the Steel Bowl and was played at Legion Field.[3]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vulcan_Bowl</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeonnam Dragons</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jeonnam_Dragons</link><description>The Jeonnam Dragons (Korean: 전남 드래곤즈 FC) are a South Korean professional football club based in the city of Gwangyang, South Jeolla Province that competes in the K League 2, the second tier of South Korean football. The Dragons play their home matches at the Gwangyang Football Stadium, one of the first football-specific stadiums in South Korea. They have won the Korean FA Cup four times (1997, 2006, 2007 and 2021) and were the runners-up of K League in 1997. They also reached the final of the 1998–99 Asian Cup Winners' Cup, where they lost to Al Ittihad.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jeonnam_Dragons</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dictyonosteus</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dictyonosteus</link><description>Dictyonosteus is a genus of prehistoric coelacanth fish which lived during the Late Devonian period. Fossils have been found in Spitsbergen, Norway.[1]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dictyonosteus</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>