<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Wiki en.wikipedia.org</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org</link><description>Hi</description><atom:link href="https://en.wikipedia.org" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:35:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>The Story of Diva and Flea</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Story_of_Diva_and_Flea</link><description>The Story of Diva and Flea is a 2015 children's book written by Mo Willems and it is illustrated by Tony DiTerlizzi. It was first published by Hyperion Books for Children.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Story_of_Diva_and_Flea</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LG enV Touch</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/LG_enV_Touch</link><description>The LG enV Touch, also known as the Voyager 2 or VX11000, is an internet-enabled, multimedia device created by LG Electronics for use with Verizon Wireless. The phone was released on June 5, 2009 as a successor to the LG Voyager. The phone's external screen is touch enabled with a virtual keyboard and buttons. The internal screen features a QWERTY keyboard and both screens have a WVGA resolution. The phone's functions include a 3.2-megapixel camera with flash, a portable media player, text messaging, e-mail support, a web browser, a built-in accelerometer, and Verizon's GPS navigation software, VZ Navigator. It is a dual-band CDMA phone using EVDO for data communications.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/LG_enV_Touch</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Crescent Lake (Maine)</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crescent_Lake_(Maine)</link><description>Crescent Lake (formerly known as Rattlesnake Pond) is a lake in Raymond, Maine, United States. It is located around 3.5 miles (5.6 km) north of the center of Raymond. A few other lakes surround it, including Panther Pond to the south (to which it is connected by the Tenny River), Raymond Pond to the east, Thompson Lake to the north and Dumpling Pond and Coffee Pond to the west. It has a surface area of 716 acres (3 km2) and a maximum depth of 54 ft (16 m),[2] which occurs in its northeastern section. Its shoreline runs for 8.9 miles (14.3 km).[3]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crescent_Lake_(Maine)</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kryptos koehleri</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kryptos_koehleri</link><description>Kryptos koehleri is a species of sea snail, a marine gastropod mollusc in the family Colidae, the true whelks and the like.[1]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kryptos_koehleri</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>From This Place</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/From_This_Place</link><description>From This Place is a studio album by American jazz guitarist Pat Metheny, released in February 2020 on the Nonesuch label.[6]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/From_This_Place</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>