<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Wiki en.wikipedia.org</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org</link><description>Hi</description><atom:link href="https://en.wikipedia.org" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:29:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Binyomin Jacobs</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Binyomin_Jacobs</link><description>Binyomin Jacobs (born 1949 in Amsterdam), is a Dutch rabbi who lives in Amersfoort, Netherlands. At the end of 2008 he was appointed Chief Rabbi of the IPOR resort of the Netherlands, this resort includes all the municipalities of the Netherlands, except the cities of Amsterdam, Rotterdam and The Hague.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Binyomin_Jacobs</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>21st Independent Spirit Awards</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/21st_Independent_Spirit_Awards</link><description>The 21st Independent Spirit Awards, honoring the best in independent filmmaking for 2005, were announced on March 4, 2006.  It was hosted by Sarah Silverman.[1][2][3][4][5]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/21st_Independent_Spirit_Awards</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Unfinished Painting</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unfinished_Painting</link><description>Unfinished Painting is a 1989 painting by American artist Keith Haring. It is a 100 cm by 100 cm acrylic painting on canvas piece, recognizable by the large swath of canvas left exposed.[1] It is known as one of Haring's final paintings before his 1990 death from AIDS-related complications at the age of 31.[2] From April 27 to September 8, 2024, the piece was on tour with the "Keith Haring: Art Is for Everybody" exhibit at the Walker Art Center.[3]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unfinished_Painting</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bau: Artist at War</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bau:_Artist_at_War</link><description>Bau: Artist at War is a 2024 American biographical romance drama film directed by Sean McNamara and starring Emile Hirsch as Holocaust survivor Joseph Bau and Inbar Lavi as his wife Rebecca. The film also stars Josh Zuckerman, Yan Tual, Eugene Lipinski, Josh Blacker, Edward Foy, Chris Cope and Adam Tsekhman, and chronicles Bau's imprisonment in the Kraków-Płaszów concentration camp during World War II, and his subsequent relationship and wedding with Rebecca.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bau:_Artist_at_War</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mohammad Ansari (footballer)</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mohammad_Ansari_(footballer)</link><description>Mohammad Ansari (Persian: محمد انصاری, born September 23, 1991, in Tehran, Iran) is an Iranian football player, who currently plays for Mes Rafsanjan in Persian Gulf Pro League.[1] Ansari had been a key player in Persepolis in the recent years and helped the Reds win back-to-back titles in Iran league.He is also known for his positions in favor of the hardliners of the Islamic Republic.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mohammad_Ansari_(footballer)</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>