<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Wiki en.wikipedia.org</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org</link><description>Hi</description><atom:link href="https://en.wikipedia.org" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:12:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Rouse Hill</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rouse_Hill</link><description>Rouse Hill (/ˈraʊz/) is a suburb of Sydney, in the state of New South Wales, Australia. Rouse Hill is located in the Hills District, 43 kilometres north-west of the Sydney central business district and 19 kilometres north-west of the Parramatta central business district. It is in the local government areas of The Hills Shire and City of Blacktown. Rouse Hill Town Centre is at the heart of the suburb, which contains a busy Town Square.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rouse_Hill</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:00:00 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>Lørenskog IK</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%C3%B8renskog_IK</link><description>Lørenskog Ishockeyklubb (founded in 1963) is a Norwegian professional ice hockey team based in Lørenskog, Norway. The team competed in GET-ligaen from 2008 to 2018. In May 2018, the club did not receive a new licence, due to long-term economic problems.[1] The team got promoted back to the Fjordkraft-ligaen.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%C3%B8renskog_IK</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:00:00 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>Water miscible oil paint</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Water_miscible_oil_paint</link><description>Water-miscible oil paint (also called water-soluble oil paint or water-mixable oil paint) is oil paint either engineered or to which an emulsifier has been added, allowing it to be thinned and cleaned up with water.[1][2] These paints make it possible to avoid using, or at least reduce volatile organic compounds such as turpentine that may be harmful if inhaled.  Water-miscible oil paint can be mixed and applied using the same techniques as traditional oil-based paint, but while still wet it can be removed from brushes, palettes, and rags with ordinary soap and water. One of the ways its water solubility comes from is the use of an oil medium in which one end of the molecule has been engineered to be hydrophilic and thus bind loosely to water molecules, as in a solution.[3][4]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Water_miscible_oil_paint</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:00:00 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>Granite Real Estate</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Granite_Real_Estate</link><description>Granite Real Estate Investment Trust (formerly MI Developments Inc.) is a Canadian-based REIT engaged in the acquisition, development, ownership and management of industrial, warehouse and logistics properties in North America and Europe.  It was originally composed principally of former holdings of Magna International.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Granite_Real_Estate</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:00:00 +1100</pubDate></item><item><title>Embassy of Estonia, Moscow</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Embassy_of_Estonia,_Moscow</link><description>Embassy of Estonia in Moscow (Russian: Посольство Эстонии в Москве, Estonian: Eesti Suursaatkond Moskvas) is the chief diplomatic mission of Estonia in the Russian Federation. It is located at 5 Maly Kislovsky Lane (Russian: Малый Кисловский пер. 5) in the Presnensky District of Moscow.[1]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Embassy_of_Estonia,_Moscow</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:00:00 +1100</pubDate></item></channel></rss>