<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Wiki en.wikipedia.org</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org</link><description>Hi</description><atom:link href="https://en.wikipedia.org" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:25:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Christian Vegetarian Association</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christian_Vegetarian_Association</link><description>The Christian Vegetarian Association (CVA) is an international, interdenominational Christian vegetarian organization that promotes responsible stewardship of God's creation through plant-based eating. The CVA claims to advocate vegetarianism from a biblically-based, Christian perspective and sees dietary choice as a valid way to bear witness to Christ's ministry of love, peace, mercy and compassion, and prepare for the Peaceable Kingdom as foretold in the Bible.[1]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christian_Vegetarian_Association</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mian Mahalleh-ye Rudboneh</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mian_Mahalleh-ye_Rudboneh</link><description>Mian Mahalleh-ye Rudboneh (Persian: ميان محله رودبنه)[a] is a village in Rudboneh Rural District[4] of Rudboneh District in Lahijan County, Gilan province, Iran.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mian_Mahalleh-ye_Rudboneh</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Operation Tempus Veritatis</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operation_Tempus_Veritatis</link><description>Operation Tempus Veritatis (Latin for "time of truth")[1] was a Federal Police operation in Brazil in February 2024 that led to the preventive arrest of military officers and aides of former president Jair Bolsonaro.[2] The operation also executed search and seizure warrants against several targets, including four former ministers. Launched on February 8, the operation followed a plea bargain signed by Mauro Cid with a Federal Police researcher. The operation was based on a video seized from a computer belonging to Mauro Cid, documenting a meeting held on July 5, 2022, between former president Jair Bolsonaro and his ministers.[3]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operation_Tempus_Veritatis</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Open bite malocclusion</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_bite_malocclusion</link><description>Open bite is a type of orthodontic malocclusion which has been estimated to occur in 0.6% of the people in the United States. This type of malocclusion has no vertical overlap or contact between the anterior incisors.[1] The term "open bite" was coined by Carevelli in 1842 as a distinct classification of malocclusion.[2][3] Different authors have described the open bite in a variety of ways.[4] Some authors have suggested that open bite often arises when overbite is less than the usual amount. Additionally, others have contended that open bite is identified by end-on incisal relationships. Lastly, some researchers have stated that a lack of incisal contact must be present to diagnose an open bite.[5][6]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_bite_malocclusion</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Laetoria gens</title><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laetoria_gens</link><description>The gens Laetoria was a plebeian family at ancient Rome.  Its members appear regularly throughout the history of the Republic.  None of the Laetorii ever obtained the consulship, but several achieved lesser offices of the Roman state.[1]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laetoria_gens</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>